https://fourgroups.com/contact/privacy-and-legal/

PredictivePeopleManagementFour Groups Predictive People ManagementHomeChallengesTeamwork and EngagementCreate High Performing TeamsMaximise Engagement and CollaborationRecruitment and SelectionRecruit for Attitude and Train for SkillsImprove the Success Rate of Selection ProcessesPerformance ManagementObjective Performance ManagementLink Behaviour to KPIs and Financial MetricsChange ManagementImprove the Success Rate of Change ManagementOptimise the Human Factors in Business ProcessesCulture and StrategyAlign Culture and StrategyLink Human Factors to their Operational EquivalentsTraining and DevelopmentGenerate Economies of Scale and Economies of LearningCreate an Individually Personalised Training and Development SyllabusThe InnovationCurrent Perceptions of HRThe Untapped Potential of RelationshipsPredictive People Management4G’s Unique Capabilities6 New People Management ProcessesNew ProcessesTeam Creation and Group CohesionHire for Optimal RelationshipsObjective Performance ManagementPredictive Change ManagementCulture and Strategy AlignmentA Training and Development SyllabusOther Applications of 4G4GSocial ProfilesSocial RelationshipsSocial GroupsThe Visual Team BuilderRelationship FrictionCoaching ModulesValidity and ReliabilityDownloadsBrochuresVideosWhite PapersCase StudiesPress ClippingsQuarterly UpdatesQuarterly Updates SubscriptionPartnersBlogContact Privacy and LegalPrivacy Statement of Four Groups LtdInformation about our Organisation and Web siteModern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like Four Groups Ltd. We are based in the United Kingdom. Our principal activities are:Management ConsultingPsychologyOur privacy policy covers Four Groups Ltd and its Web siteThe services and links of our Web siteOur Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.Automatic Collection of InformationWe automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes:Customer administrationMarketingWe use temporary cookies that last up to thirty minutes to store personal data.Data Collection and Purpose SpecificationWe collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We may also collect information about you from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please see the end of this document. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.Children's PrivacyWe do not knowingly collect personal data from children.Disclosure and Visitor ChoiceWe do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.Confidentiality and SecurityWe have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:Unauthorised accessImproper use or disclosureUnauthorised modificationUnlawful destruction or accidental lossAll our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to Government Institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.Access to the personal data we may hold about youYou can ask us, by visiting http://www.fourgroups.com, whether we are keeping personal data about you. Upon request, we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week, although we will require proof of your identity. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:Rectified or amendedCompletedPrivacy ComplianceOur privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Four Groups operates under the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998. In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are subject to Government Agency supervision.Government Agency supervisionThe Information Commissioner http://www.dataprotection.gov.ukIf you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at our website http://www.fourgroups.comTable of personal data collected and purposes for which they are usedTable 1Personal DataResearch & DevelopmentCustomer AdminMarketingNameXXXGenderXXXTable 2Business InformationResearch & DevelopmentCustomer AdminMarketingEmployerXXXJob TitleXXXEmailXXXTelephoneXXXTable 3Other InformationResearch & DevelopmentCustomer AdministrationPersonal DetailsXXGeneralFour Groups Ltd, Company Number 4650494, VAT Number 817 7962 85, Registered in England and Wales. This website is for informational purposes only. FOUR GROUPS LTD MAKES NO WARRANTIES, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED in this website. The following are trademarks of Four Groups Ltd in the United Kingdom and/or in other countries. Four Groups, 4G, Social Profiles, Social Relationships, Social Groups, Visual Team Builder, Relationship Friction, 1Fe, 1Ne, 1Si, 1Ti, 2Fe, 2Ni, 2Se, 2Ti, 3Fi, 3Ni, 3Se, 3Te, 4Fi, 4Ne, 4Si, 4Te, Relationships of Action, Relationships of Assistance, Relationships of Association, Relationships of Balance, Relationships of Comfort, Relationships of Contrast, Relationships of Discovery, Relationships of Focus, Relationships of Interpretation, Relationships of Order, Relationships of Pairs, Relationships of Reflection, Relationships of Semi-Balance, Relationships of Similarity. All other brands and trademarks are the property of their respective owners. Other names appearing on this website may be the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners in the UK and other countries. All trademarks used are properties of their respective owners.CopyrightCopyright Four Groups Ltd. All rights reserved. No part of this website may be reproduced without express written permission from Four Groups Ltd.Terms and ConditionsThis website is owned by Four Groups Ltd and is made available to users on the following terms and conditions. All terms and conditions are to be interpreted under the laws of England, and by continuing to use or access this site you agree and accept these terms and conditions. Four Groups Ltd may, at its discretion, modify, revise, or change these terms and conditions at any time by changing the text of this page.Privacy and Data ProtectionFour Groups operates under the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998.Licence to useFour Groups Ltd grants you a non-exclusive licence to access the content of this website. However any reproduction, distribution, or commercial use of any content is not permitted without the prior agreement of Four Groups Ltd. By using this site, you acknowledge and accept that the copyright, database rights and all other intellectual property rights comprised in, or relating to this website and the data contained within it, belongs to Four Groups Ltd.DisclaimerFour Groups Ltd makes efforts to ensure that the information contained on this website is accurate and up to date. However Four Groups Ltd cannot take responsibility for any loss, financial or otherwise, inconvenience, or subsequent loss caused by reliance on inaccurate material or information contained on this website.Third party website linksThis website may at times contain links to websites operated by parties other than Four Groups Ltd. These links are provided for the convenience of users of the website only. Four Groups Ltd does not control the content of these third party websites and is not responsible for their content. The inclusion of links by Four Groups Ltd to these websites does not imply any endorsement by Four Groups Ltd of the material held by the websites. You are solely responsible for evaluating the accuracy and completeness of any information provided by third party websites, and also the value and integrity of any goods and services offered by third party websitesLimitation of LiabilityFour Groups Ltd excludes all warranties and conditions with regard to the material, information and any goods or services supplied in relation to the website, whether express, implied, or statutory. This includes implied warranties and conditions of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. In no event shall Four Groups Ltd be liable for any indirect, punitive, special, incidental, or consequential damages whatsoever even if Four Groups Ltd has been advised of the possibility of damages including, without limitation, damages for loss of use, data or profits arising out of or in any way connected with the use or performance of the website, interruptions or delays to the website, the provision of or failure to provide services, or any information, material, goods and services obtained through the website, whether based on contract, tort or otherwise to the fullest extent permitted by law.VirusesFour Groups Ltd makes all reasonable attempts to exclude viruses from the website. However it cannot ensure such exclusion, and no liability is accepted for damage caused by, or through, the downloading of viruses. Four Groups Ltd recommends that you take all appropriate safeguards before downloading information from this website.TwitterLinkedinFacebookemailQuick Links
3 Minute Visual Team Builder Demo
Arrange a Sales MeetingPlease complete the form to arrange a sales meetingFirst Name *requiredLast Name *requiredEmail *requiredTelephoneOrganisationTitleSuitable Dates and Optional CommentsAnti Spam  Download a BrochurePlease complete the form to download our brochureFirst Name *requiredLast Name *requiredEmail *requiredTelephoneOrganisationTitleAnti Spam Latest Blog Posts Hiring and Acquiring – Two Sides of the Same Coin? HR and Big Data; Jumping the Gun? Rethinking the War for TalentNewsletterFirst Name *requiredLast Name *requiredEmail *requiredAnti Spam Site Search Search for:
Quick NavigationHomeChallengesThe InnovationNew Processes4GDownloadsPartnersBlogContact and LegalContactPrivacy and LegalFour GroupsPredictive People Management© 2004 -
Four Groups Ltd WordPress ThemesWe use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
